

INTRODUCTION

Focused on simplifying my work, and the work of others. Every day is a day I will learn something about a project and the people building it. Appreciator of app architecture. Always researching easier ways to do complicated things.

EXPERIENCE

Software developer

EDEDOC, Angoulême, France

Jan. 2021 - Present

- Created mobile apps with Flutter. Understood the framework structure. Connected the apps to middleware. Handled user accounts and authentication. Published apps to Android and iOS stores.
- Designed app screens. Adjusted them according to the team's advice. Attention to detail and ergonomy.
- Tested multiple edge cases in order to solidify my knowledge of the company's middleware. Documented code and app build process.

Game developer intern

Rebound CG, Angouleme, France

Mar. 2020 - Sept. 2020 6 months

- Developed user interfaces and connected them to the game framework for data display. Added functions to the game framework to treat data according to the design documents.
- Version control and code reviews. Learned to understand the other person's way of thinking during code reviews.
- Developed patience, focus and perseverance.

Web developer intern

VPN Autos, Bordeaux, France

Apr. 2017 - Jun. 2017 3 months

- Acquired knowledge on how computers communicate on the internet, how to use protocols and middleware.
- Created a website prototype. I was in charge of designing pages and connecting the website to the database.

CONTACT

Phone

+33 6 52 24 21 63

Email

jorge.noogueira@gmail.com

LinkedIn

linkedin.com/in/j-nogueira

Address

Appartement 113, 51, Boulevard d'Auvergne 16000, Angoulême France

EDUCATION

Cnam-Enjmin 2018-2020 Angoulême - France Game programming

Université de Bordeaux 2017-2018 - France

Computer science theory

IUT de Bordeaux 2015-2017 - France

Technical and professional knowledge in computer science

SKILLS

User interfaces design Learning and teaching Documentation Autonomous